BONFACE KANYENJE

00000 Nairobi, Kenya | mainaboniface221@gmai.com | +254797153028

Skills

Front-end Back-end

HTML,CSS,React,Angular and Javascript Python, Django ,Flask, Postgresql and Sqlite

Summary

Committed professional offering more than 2 years of experience in the field of web application development. Excellent communication skills and a consistent team player in all sorts of environments. Seeking to expand talents by bringing a wealth of expertise to a well-established company.

Professional Experience			
03/2022 - present	 Freelance Web Developer, Upwork Contributed to back-end experience and collaborated on APIs. Created awesome sites for my clients Worked on multiple projects with deadlines but I was able to maneuver Debugged sites 	Nairobi, Kenya	
04/2021 - 08/2021	Huduma Number, Govt Kenya Collected information on Users and successfully submitted to the servers	Nairobi, Kenya	

Education			
01/2021 - 07/2022	Software Engineering (web) Web developer, Moringa School	Nairobi, Kenya	
04/2019	Bachelor of Science Electrical Engineering, Dedan Kimathi University	Nyeri, Kenya	
01/2014 - 11/2018	KCSE, Karima Boy's High School	Nyeri, Kenya	
01/2006 - 11/2014	KCPE, Ruai Primary School	Nyeri, Kenya	

Interests

Football, Movies